[Music]
MP3 Hello Ajay Hello
everyone welcome to my YouTube
channel Our topic today is ICC
Lombard has made some changes in its previous health
insurance policy ICC Lombard Health. I am talking
about
that ICC Lombard is
a very big name in general insurance companies and their claim
settlement is also very good. So by
adding this feature they have made their policy plan
quite attractive. Today we will
subscribe to the details of the same, which will know
what are the features and how much extra you will have to pay for it.
People have subscribed to that Reset
Benefits product which was available earlier also
which means that if you have also decided to get Rs
5 lakh as soon as you become Bigg Boss, then the
company will reset it again. Earlier
they used to do it only once. Now
after the new feature of the company, you
can avail the Easy Teacher benefit of this Reset Benefits unlimited times. You
must keep one thing in mind that Reset
Benefits does not subscribe. Now let's talk about the
second feature which is Organ Donor  And it
means that if any person donates to you, then the person who
subscribes to the company,
earlier organ donor was not covered in this policy,
now this organ donor is threatened, now the
school maximum is 10th,
now let's talk about the third feature which is
your air ambulance service policy, in this the
facility of air ambulance was not available
but now these people have made ambulance available which
you can use, the
point of this is your
ambulance charges, earlier the ambulance
charges you used to get were only 1500 rupees,
now the ambulance charges you will get will be one per cent
of minute or you
can get maximum 1000 ambulances
which you will get on hospitalization, if you
subscribe to Agrotech which means
additional sum insured product then the
company
gives you no claim bonus, if you have come below 50 thousand in the past there used to be
two no claim bonuses,
on making a claim it will not be Bigg Boss,
your amount will remain
200, now after this policy feature you will
not get no claim bonus  If your
plan is more, then let's talk about your treatment.
Treatment means
that if such a situation arises in front of you that the
hospital
is not available here or you are
not in a situation to reach the hospital, then you
can get treatment from your home in this channel, which is war
now school subscribe. If
you are pregnant, then you can
consult with the doctor through video conferencing,
he will guide you well on
how you should deal with the question.
Seven features which ICC has now
in iHealth, apart from this, there are many features
which you can additionally appoint,
subscribe separately. Now let's talk about
how much extra you will have to
subscribe to, that on an
average you will have to pay around 12 to 15-16 percent
extra to
avail the benefits of this policy feature
and our existing customers of ICC
can avail the benefits of this policy feature. New 2018
means January 2021 IF Policy To Help
Service  There will be service charge. There have been appreciable
changes in the ICC policy. We keep bringing all this
information about the changes in the districts.
So please
like and subscribe to our channel.
[Music]